{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807283599","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807283599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lima"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807289474","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807289474"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lima"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807289833","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807289833"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lima"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807293256","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807293256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tembo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" mbo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807293734","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807293733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tembo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" mbo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807299848","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807299848"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tembo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" te"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807300395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807300395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tembo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbo"," userResponse":" mbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807304543","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807304543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zeze"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807304774","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807304774"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zeze"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807308162","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807308162"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chai"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807309366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807309366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chai"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807310863","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807310863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chai"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807314028","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807314028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_paka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807315524","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807315524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_paka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807316465","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807316465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_paka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807319024","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807319023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zizi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807319425","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807319425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zizi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807322829","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807322829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bega"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" be"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807323119","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807323119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bega"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" be"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807329004","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807329004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bega"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" be"," userResponse":" be"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807329962","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807329962"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bega"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807332623","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807332623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_embe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807333349","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807333348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_embe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807334306","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807334306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_embe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807336882","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807336881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lala"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807337454","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807337454"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lala"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807340423","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807340423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chu"," userResponse":" chu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807341080","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807341080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngwa"," userResponse":" ngwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807343247","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807343247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 8ac6be3f-1ce6-47c5-99df-9149a953e5ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807353823","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807353823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 391e3812-7fcf-4a19-8df5-d68c566ca9a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807355895","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807355894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 391e3812-7fcf-4a19-8df5-d68c566ca9a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807374670","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807374670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807390083","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807390083"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807394150","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807394150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807406413","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807406413"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807415000","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807415000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807426382","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807426382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807426608","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807426607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807437604","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807437604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807446647","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807446647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807460045","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807460045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807464085","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807464085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807468962","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807468962"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807478631","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807478631"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807489017","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807489017"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807494778","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807494777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807502309","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807502309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807513173","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807513173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807530395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807530395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807533257","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807533256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807544353","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807544353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807544676","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807544676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807546962","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807546962"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807547918","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807547918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807553241","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807553241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807553487","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807553487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807564939","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807564939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807570510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807570510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807579441","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807579441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807586626","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807586625"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807594589","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807594589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807605433","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807605432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807609476","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807609476"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807616190","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807616190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807627298","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807627298"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807637055","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807637055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807650322","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807650322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-4.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807655473","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807655473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" c9d2843b-5b62-4dc9-929c-cfa627c15db0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-4.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_hivi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807664451","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807664450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 3aba3569-7110-4e42-88fa-16a18fb71c54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807664688","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807664687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 3aba3569-7110-4e42-88fa-16a18fb71c54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807665319","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807665319"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 3aba3569-7110-4e42-88fa-16a18fb71c54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807665403","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807665403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" 3aba3569-7110-4e42-88fa-16a18fb71c54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807679151","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807679151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ndevu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807680092","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807680092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ndevu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vu"," userResponse":" vu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807683157","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807683156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kaa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807688647","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807688647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kaa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807689869","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807689869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kaa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807693310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807693309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nzi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807694146","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807694146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nzi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807697373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807697372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807698047","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807698046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807699971","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807699971"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807704215","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807704215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807704564","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807704564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807707783","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807707783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mamba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807708687","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807708687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mamba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807710107","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807710107"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mamba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807714292","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807714292"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_boga"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bo"," userResponse":" bo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807714589","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807714589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_boga"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807718301","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807718301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwembe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwe"," userResponse":" mwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807718986","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807718985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwembe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807722374","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807722374"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jembe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" je"," userResponse":" je"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807722749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807722749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jembe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807725924","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807725924"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kombe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807726222","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807726222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kombe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807728565","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807728564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_kombe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807737893","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807737892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_kombe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807746808","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807746808"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_kombe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807755603","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807755603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" a9403d06-bd1a-451e-8638-468fcac3edc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_kombe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807766542","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807766542"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" b61c4985-13eb-4c02-ae92-6020db800df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndio_nane-ndio-kila"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndio"," userResponse":" nane"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807772361","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807772360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" b61c4985-13eb-4c02-ae92-6020db800df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndio_nane-ndio-kila"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndio"," userResponse":" kila"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807777853","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807777853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" b61c4985-13eb-4c02-ae92-6020db800df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndio_nane-ndio-kila"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndio"," userResponse":" ndio"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807783671","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807783670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" b61c4985-13eb-4c02-ae92-6020db800df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naye"," userResponse":" wana"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807786675","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807786675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" b61c4985-13eb-4c02-ae92-6020db800df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807795389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807795388"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" b61c4985-13eb-4c02-ae92-6020db800df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807803573","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807803572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" b61c4985-13eb-4c02-ae92-6020db800df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807828848","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807828848"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" b61c4985-13eb-4c02-ae92-6020db800df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807834878","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807834878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" b61c4985-13eb-4c02-ae92-6020db800df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549807843427","data":{"timestamp":" 1549807843427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_165856"," gameId":" b61c4985-13eb-4c02-ae92-6020db800df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}